gamedoss.com 2010-12-25

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
The privacy of our visitors is extremely important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of information received and collected by us and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other websites, our server makes use of log files. The log files record data such as the internet protocol (IP) addresses of our visitors and pages viewed. Although each user will have a unique IP address, this is never linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies / Flash Shared Objects / Web Beacons**  
To enable an enhanced user experience, we store some information about visitor preferences, browser language, the number of games played etc. The games may also store data for such purposes as recording user preferences, and saving level progress etc. Unless a user specifically enters personal data, no data stored is personally identifiable.

**Advertising Networks**  
From time-to-time we may use third party ad networks. We do not have control of or access to cookies that are used by these networks. If you wish to disable or selectively turn off cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

**Google AdSense / DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
